Everyone's obsessed with Claude code, but for designers like you and me, what does that mean for us?So today we're going to look at what it is, what to know, how to set it up, how to use it, and how to make the most of it.Let's get started.Real quick before we begin, if you're a big fan of myself, what we're doing here at UI Collective, you can check out our website.I'll put a link for this in the description.
每個人都在瘋 Claude Code，但對於像你我這樣的設計師來說，這對我們意味著什麼？所以今天我們要來看看它是什麼、需要知道什麼、如何設定、如何使用，以及如何發揮它的最大價值。讓我們開始吧。在開始之前先快速說一下，如果你很喜歡我和我們在 UI Collective 做的事情，可以去看看我們的網站。我會在影片描述中放上連結。
And consider supporting the academy where you get access to a bunch of great courses, a bunch of great micro lessons, private Slack channel access for me and the team, and some great downloads too.Or whether you just want to join the community, it's totally free to join the community.You can ask any questions on ourcommunity forum.I respond to everyone that's on there.Also get access to some great savings and some great resources too.So whether you want to join the community or you want to support the academy, hope to see you online.Really appreciate you being here.It's rock and roll.
也請考慮支持我們的學院，在那裡你可以獲得一系列很棒的課程、許多優質的微課程、我和團隊的私人 Slack 頻道存取權限，還有一些很棒的下載資源。或者如果你只是想加入社群，加入社群完全免費。你可以在我們的社群論壇上提出任何問題。我會回覆論壇上的每個人。還能獲得一些很棒的優惠和資源。所以無論你想加入社群還是支持學院，希望在網路上見到你。非常感謝你的參與。開搞吧。
Also made it a goal for the year to start posting more on X and hyping up other designers.So I'll put a link to my X in the video description.Interact with me on there, share your designs.I'll hype you up.I'll give you feedback, whatever you need.Follow me.All right, my people.Design and Claude, using Claude to design, let's go over what to know.Let's dive right in.So Claude code is all the hype these days.
我也把今年的目標定為更頻繁地在 X 上發文，並且為其他設計師加油打氣。所以我會在影片描述中放上我的 X 連結。在上面跟我互動，分享你的設計作品。我會幫你宣傳。我會給你回饋，不管你需要什麼。追蹤我吧。好了，各位。設計與 Claude，用 Claude 來做設計，讓我們來看看需要知道什麼。直接切入正題。Claude Code 最近超級火紅。
If you go on X, you go on any social media site, and you're involved in the tech space, all everyone's doing is just hyping up Claude code and what they're able to produce with Claude code.But what does this mean for us as designers?Because again, a lot of us, majority of us, don't have the level of technical know-how in order to operate some of these tools at a way in which we see a lot of people online do it.
如果你去 X 上看，去任何社群媒體網站，而且你身在科技圈，每個人都在瘋狂推崇 Claude Code 以及他們用 Claude Code 能做出什麼東西。但這對我們設計師來說意味著什麼？因為說實在的，我們很多人，大多數人，並沒有足夠的技術知識來像我們在網路上看到很多人那樣操作這些工具。
Now, it's important to note that if you see people online being like, oh, look what I spun up with Claude code, doesn't mean it's perfect in Figma.Doesn't mean it's going to replace you as a designer.It just means that they were able to build something cool with AI.So just because Claude is for more technical users does not mean that you should ignore it.The one thing you don't want to do right now
現在，重要的是要注意，如果你看到有人在網路上說，噢，看看我用 Claude Code 做出了什麼，這不代表它在 Figma 裡是完美的。也不代表它會取代你這個設計師。這只是說明他們用 AI 建構了一些很酷的東西。所以，不要因為 Claude 是給更技術導向的使用者用的，就認為你應該忽視它。你現在最不該做的一件事
in the design ecosystem is to ignore AI, ignore the tools that developers are hyped about, because eventually those tools are going to get wrapped in some type of design interface, and then all of a sudden you're far behind.So just because it's for more tactical users does not mean that you should ignore it.And we're going to cover what to do so that you're not ignoring it throughout this video, but I just want to preface with that right away.Now, what is it that you should know?First off, that there's no design interface for Claude code.
就是在設計生態系中忽視 AI，忽視那些讓開發者興奮的工具，因為這些工具最終會被包裝成某種設計介面，然後你突然就落後了。所以不要因為它是給更偏技術的使用者用的就忽視它。我們會在這支影片中介紹該怎麼做，讓你不會忽視它，但我只是想先把這點說在前面。那麼，你應該知道什麼呢？首先，Claude Code 沒有設計介面。
If you're expecting Claude code to have like a Figma type interface,
如果你期待 Claude Code 有類似 Figma 那樣的介面，
You can run it in cursor, you can run it into VS Code, Cloud Code is a desktop app, you can run it out of your terminal, but there's no true design interface that us as designers might be expecting.Now, when prompted right, the designs it produces can be fantastic, but again, it does take work to get there.What you'll see on X is a lot of people posting what they've produced,But they don't like tell you the effort that was involved in order to get to that design.
你可以在 Cursor 裡跑它，可以在 VS Code 裡跑它，Claude Code 是一個桌面應用程式，你可以在終端機裡跑它，但沒有真正的設計介面是我們設計師可能期望的那種。不過，當提示詞下得好的時候，它產出的設計可以非常棒，但同樣地，要達到那個水準是需要花功夫的。你在 X 上看到的是很多人發佈他們做出的成果，但他們不會告訴你為了達到那個設計所付出的努力。
It's usually just, oh, we built this with Claude code and everyone thinks it can just one shot like a five star design.It looks like it came out of Google or Apple.Can't do that.But when prompted right, the designs it produces can really be good.You know, it's a really great model.And now it also has a two way sync with Figma, meaning I can do the prompting in Claude, push it via Figma MCP into a Figma file.
通常只是說，噢，我們用 Claude Code 做了這個，然後每個人都以為它能一次就產出五星級的設計。看起來像是 Google 或 Apple 出品的。做不到的。但當提示詞下得好的時候，它產出的設計確實可以非常好。你知道的，這是一個非常強大的模型。而且現在它還有跟 Figma 的雙向同步功能，意思是我可以在 Claude 裡下提示詞，透過 Figma MCP 推送到 Figma 檔案裡。
iterate on it in Figma, maybe show a client in Figma, make some changes in Figma, and then pull that back into Claude.So you can see how powerful that is for a lot of designers and a lot of developers.Introducing this into the workflow where I can do a lot of the heavy lifting in Claude, do a lot of the minor elements in Figma, then bring it back into Claude and iterate that way.Now, Claude code is not like a
在 Figma 裡迭代，也許在 Figma 裡展示給客戶看，在 Figma 裡做一些修改，然後再把那些變更拉回 Claude。所以你可以看到這對很多設計師和開發者來說有多強大。把這個引入工作流程，我可以在 Claude 裡做大量的重活，在 Figma 裡做一些細節元素，然後再帶回 Claude 用這種方式迭代。那麼，Claude Code 不等同於
short form for Claude Opus 4.6, whatever Claude model that's out there by the time you're watching this video.There's a fundamental difference between the two.First off, Claude code, it's sort of the an agentic tool that runs in your terminal or runs on like the Claude app or whatever.So it has direct access to your file system tools so it can do things, not just suggest things.It can make changes to files.It can...
Claude Opus 4.6 的簡稱，或者你看這支影片時出了什麼新的 Claude 模型。兩者之間有根本性的差異。首先，Claude Code 算是一個在你的終端機或 Claude 桌面應用程式等環境中運行的代理工具。所以它可以直接存取你的檔案系統和工具，意味著它能實際執行操作，不只是提供建議。它可以修改檔案。它可以...
understandings.It can build Figma designs, right?Like that's part of like where that two-way sync comes from.But Claude, you know, Model X, you know, in this case, Claude Opus 4.6, it's the underlying...language model of Claude.So it's like the brain.So it takes text in, produces text out.On its own, it has no ability to actually read the files, interact with your system.But Claude code can read files, update files, interact with your system in a way that the Claude model itself cannot.
進行各種理解和操作。它可以建構 Figma 設計，對吧？那就是雙向同步的由來。但 Claude，你知道的，某某模型，在這個例子裡是 Claude Opus 4.6，它是底層的...語言模型。所以它就像是大腦。它接收文字輸入，產生文字輸出。它本身沒有能力去實際讀取檔案、與你的系統互動。但 Claude Code 可以讀取檔案、更新檔案，以一種 Claude 模型本身做不到的方式與你的系統互動。
Just wanted to clarify that because it's a pretty fundamental difference and where a lot of designers get mixed up.Now let's go ahead and set up.Claude code and then connect Figma MCP.So it's a little bit different than how we might have connected Figma MCP to something like cursor in the past.Now, we're going to do this actually via our device terminal.More on that in just a second.And I'll put a link for their docs down below.So just scroll down here and find the operating system that you're on.
我只是想釐清這一點，因為這是一個相當根本的差異，也是很多設計師搞混的地方。現在讓我們來設定 Claude Code，然後連接 Figma MCP。這跟我們過去在 Cursor 之類的工具中連接 Figma MCP 的方式有點不同。我們實際上要透過裝置的終端機來做這件事。稍後會詳細說明。我會在下方放上他們的文件連結。所以就往下捲到這裡，找到你使用的作業系統。
I'm on a macOS, so I would just copy this line right here because, again, this is for macOS.So I would copy that.Now, I'm not too sure how to open it on a PC because I haven't used a PC in a decade.Buton a Mac, like the very top bar, you're going to see a little search, not within Chrome, not within your browser, but at the operating system level, you're going to see a search icon at the very top.Hit that and then search terminal.
我用的是 macOS，所以我只需要複製這一行，因為這是給 macOS 用的。所以我會複製它。我不太確定在 PC 上怎麼開，因為我已經十年沒用過 PC 了。但在 Mac 上，在最上面的選單列，你會看到一個小小的搜尋圖示，不是在 Chrome 裡面，不是在瀏覽器裡面，而是在作業系統層級的最上方，你會看到一個搜尋圖示。點下去然後搜尋「終端機」。
And then with this line copied here, we're going to paste this line inside of the terminal.So you're going to land in something like this once you open up your terminal again.I'm on a Mac.So I'm just going to paste in that exact line that we got from Claude's documentation and just hit enter.Unreal, so now you can see that it's actually installed.Now, the first time I did this, I ran into issues.
然後把複製好的這一行貼到終端機裡面。當你再次打開終端機後，你會看到類似這樣的畫面。我用的是 Mac。所以我只需要把從 Claude 文件中取得的那一行指令貼進去，然後按下 Enter。太讚了，你可以看到它已經安裝好了。不過我第一次做的時候有遇到一些問題。
If you run into issues, just take a screenshot of what terminal is showing you and then just upload it to Claude or even ChatGPT and have you walk you through how to fix it.So if you get any issues, just have AI troubleshoot.So I just opened up a new terminal.Now, whenever you open up a new terminal, it's just going to appear blank.And if you want to open a Claude code instance, you have to type Claude as I did right here, and then just press enter.So if you hit type Claude, press enter, thisis going to pop up.
如果你遇到問題，只需要把終端機顯示的畫面截個圖，然後上傳到 Claude 甚至 ChatGPT，讓它引導你解決問題。所以如果遇到任何問題，就讓 AI 幫你排除故障。我剛開了一個新的終端機視窗。每次你打開新的終端機，它就是一片空白。如果你想開啟一個 Claude Code 實例，你必須像我這裡一樣輸入 Claude，然後按 Enter。所以當你輸入 Claude、按下 Enter，這個畫面就會彈出來。
It's going to show you where you have Claude installed, and now we can start to work with our Figma MCP and do everything else that we want to do.So with Claude all set up on our terminal, what we're going to want to do now is just head over to Claude's documentation.I'll put a link for this in the video description, and just come down here, just copy the...this command right here, and let's navigate back to our terminal.Let's just go ahead and paste in that command that we had just copied into a Cloud Code terminal instance here.
它會顯示你在哪裡安裝了 Claude，現在我們就可以開始使用 Figma MCP 並做其他我們想做的事情了。Claude 在終端機上設定好之後，我們接下來要做的就是前往 Claude 的文件頁面。我會在影片描述中放上連結，然後往下來到這裡，複製這個指令，讓我們回到終端機。我們把剛才複製的那個指令貼到 Claude Code 的終端機實例中。
So let's go ahead, copy, paste that in, and away we go.So assuming all was successful for you, then paste in this command right here.I'll also put a link to this command, not a link, sorry.I'll paste the command for this in the video description as well.So then just go ahead and then run that.So the show show is installed for you, and it just doesn't show that for meactually already had it installed.What you're going to want to do that, hit slash and then plug in, and this here is going to pop up.
那我們就來複製、貼上，然後開始吧。假設你這邊一切順利，那就貼上這個指令。我也會在影片描述中放上這個指令，不是連結，抱歉。我會把指令貼在影片描述中。然後就執行它吧。所以它會顯示已經為你安裝好了，只是對我來說沒有顯示，因為我之前已經安裝過了。你接下來要做的是，按斜線然後輸入 plugin，這個畫面就會彈出來。
So you're under discover, then just use the arrow keys on your keyboard, just navigate towards install, and now you're going to need to go through the process of authenticating your Figma Remote MCP server.So hit enter and go through the installation process as it will go through on screen.So then very similar to what you might have seen in some other tutorials with things like cursor and windsurf, you are going to see this type of a greenaccess page pop up inside of your browser.So just hit agree and allow access.
你會在「探索」底下，然後用鍵盤上的方向鍵移到「安裝」，現在你需要完成 Figma Remote MCP 伺服器的認證流程。按下 Enter 然後按照畫面上的安裝流程操作。接下來跟你在其他教學中看到的 Cursor 和 Windsurf 類似，你會在瀏覽器中看到這種綠色的存取許可頁面彈出來。只要點擊同意並允許存取就可以了。
But again, make sure you are agreeing and allow access on the right Figma account, especially for those who have multiple Figma accounts with multiple clients.And just like that, now we're connected to Figma via MCP to Claude.So now we can start to have some fun working with our designs.So now let's just start to test our connection and see what Claude is able to produce fromfrom our terminal inside of Figma.
但同樣地，請確保你是在正確的 Figma 帳號上同意和允許存取，特別是對於那些有多個 Figma 帳號和多個客戶的人。就這樣，現在我們透過 MCP 把 Claude 連接到 Figma 了。所以現在我們可以開始玩設計了。讓我們來測試一下連線，看看 Claude 能從我們的終端機在 Figma 裡面產出什麼東西。
So what I have just copied onto my clipboard right now is just a URL to a regular Figma file, just an empty Figma file.So let's just put in build me a black and purple dashboard for a modern SaaS company, whatever, something like that.And then just paste in the link that we're going to want.want that dashboard built inside.Again, it's just an easy, simple prompt just to get our feet wet here.So let's go ahead now and then run that.
我剛才複製到剪貼簿的就是一個普通 Figma 檔案的網址，一個空的 Figma 檔案。那我們就輸入「幫我建構一個黑紫配色的儀表板，給一家現代的 SaaS 公司用」，大概是這樣。然後貼上我們想要把儀表板建構在裡面的那個連結。同樣地，這只是一個簡單的提示詞，讓我們先暖暖身。那我們就來執行吧。
So eventually what it did is it produced, and I'm looking up here because I sort of had to move my monitor around and move it on a bigger screen so I can see both at the same time, is what it did is it built the dashboard locally, but then it also built the same dashboard inside of Figma here.So what's nice about it is I can actually take individual elements here.
最終它產出了結果，我往上看是因為我不得不把螢幕移來移去、換到更大的螢幕上才能同時看到兩邊，它做的是在本地端建構了儀表板，同時也在 Figma 裡建構了同樣的儀表板。它好的地方在於我可以實際選取裡面的個別元素。
let's select an element, let's select this, and then paste, select that, and then send that to Figma.Now, if I was to extend this out, it just takes it as is.You can see just because I'm condensed down to a screen, like it took like sort of the condensed down version.But if I was just to extend this out here, if I was just to extend this out and then copy this, select an element, I always forget to do that, and then send that to Figma.Notice how it pastes in a little bit cleaner.
讓我選取一個元素，選這個，然後貼上，選那個，然後發送到 Figma。如果我把它展開的話，它就是原樣保留。你可以看到因為我把畫面壓縮了，它就取了壓縮後的版本。但如果我把它展開，展開之後再複製這個，選取一個元素——我老是忘記做這步——然後發送到 Figma。注意到它貼上去的效果乾淨多了。
So there's something for you to take note of right there.So it's going to collapse back in.So you can take the entire screen, you can select specific elements, and what that allows you to do is sort of jam on individualelements here and not having to jam on the entire dashboard at a time.So say if there's only one element that I like here, one group, I just want to send this one group to Figma for me to riff on.I actually have that ability where it then takes that element.
所以這裡有一點值得你注意。它會收合回去。你可以選取整個畫面，也可以選取特定元素，這讓你能夠針對個別元素去調整，而不用一次調整整個儀表板。比如說如果這裡只有一個元素是我喜歡的，一個群組，我只想把這一個群組發送到 Figma 讓我去發揮。我確實有這個能力，它就會把那個元素傳過去。
So now if I really like this element, I can take the specific ones that I like that Claude Coded produced and then send that to Figma.Again, still looking up here just because I have a larger monitor for me to have more space on.But one thing I'd like to call out is that say I want to get rid of these emojis.Like I don't really like these things that are here.I can delete these, I can delete these, and I can delete these.Now, notice that it doesn't update on the Claude version, run locally right away.
所以現在如果我真的喜歡這個元素，我可以把 Claude Code 產出的特定元素挑出來，然後發送到 Figma。同樣地，我還是在看上面的螢幕，因為我用了更大的螢幕好讓我有更多空間。但有一件事我想特別提一下，假設我想去掉這些表情符號。像是我不太喜歡這些東西。我可以刪掉這些、刪掉這些、還有刪掉這些。注意到 Claude 那邊本地端的版本不會馬上更新。
So we actually need to do some prompting in order to send that back to Claude.But again, there is that two-way sync now.I'll show you in just a sec.The other thing, too, is you're going to notice is that there's still issues with perfect responsiveness.Again, like all the other AI tools that are out there and that I've covered in other videos, they don't really get it responsive perfectly for a try.If you're expecting to be like, you can get a design, you don't need to do anythingwith it perfectly responsive.
所以我們實際上需要透過下提示詞把修改發送回 Claude。但同樣地，現在確實有雙向同步的功能。我等一下會示範。另外你還會注意到響應式設計還是有問題。就像所有其他我在其他影片中介紹過的 AI 工具一樣，它們第一次嘗試都沒辦法完美做到響應式。如果你期待的是拿到設計後什麼都不用動，就能完美響應式，
Us in a way where like it's development handoff right out-of-the-box.Not there yet.Probably get there in the future, but not there yet.So let's take the changes that we made here.So I'm just going to copy.a link to this selection.Because again, what we did is we just removed those emojis because I didn't really want it.And again, you can do this at a larger scale.It would have been easy to say, Hey, remove the emojis from the top, the metrics.
直接就能交付開發那種開箱即用的程度。目前還做不到。未來可能會做到，但目前還不行。那讓我們把這裡做的修改拿來用。我先來複製這個選取範圍的連結。因為我們剛才做的就是移除了那些表情符號，因為我不太想要它們。當然你可以在更大的範圍上做這件事。比如直接說「嘿，把頂部指標上的表情符號移除」會更簡單。
But let's open back up the terminal now and take this Figma URL that we just copied and have it actually rebuild the dashboard or update the dashboard based on the changes that we had made.So now what I can do is I can back into the terminal now, so update the dashboard.
但讓我們回到終端機，拿著剛才複製的這個 Figma 網址，讓它根據我們做的修改重新建構或更新這個儀表板。所以現在我可以回到終端機，輸入「根據修改來更新儀表板」。
cards based on the changes I made here.So then I'm going to paste the link to just those Figma cards that we had tweaked.So then we're just going to send that to Claude.Then look what it came back with.It took the changes that we made to the widget in Figma and then pushed it to the developed side.How wicked.
根據我在這裡做的修改來更新卡片。然後我貼上我們剛才調整過的那些 Figma 卡片的連結。然後我們就把這個發送給 Claude。看看它回傳了什麼。它把我們在 Figma 裡對小工具做的修改同步到了開發端。太厲害了。
I know we did that on such a small scale, just removing the emojis, but how powerful of a workflow is that, especially on a larger scale where you build a design in Claude, push it to Figma, iterate with your team on the widgets, the components, everything inside Figma, even if the auto layout and stuff isn't perfect right away.And then when you're ready, tell Claude, here's the updated widgets included on the dashboards that we can show a client, a stakeholder, whoever.Come on, people.Unreal workflow.
我知道我們做的是這麼小規模的操作，只是移除表情符號，但這個工作流程有多強大啊，尤其是在更大規模的情境下——你在 Claude 裡建構一個設計，推送到 Figma，跟你的團隊在 Figma 裡迭代小工具、元件和所有東西，即使自動佈局之類的一開始不完美。然後當你準備好了，告訴 Claude，這是更新後的小工具，放到儀表板上讓我們可以展示給客戶、利害關係人看。拜託，各位。太不可思議的工作流程了。
Now, one thing that's important to note is don't condense it down as I did here, just trying to fit things on one screen.Use two monitors or else Claude will get confused around, like, maybe you want a tighter look.You want to adjust the padding.Just do it normally.Don't condense things down as I did.Now, we did all that within terminal, but Claude also has a desktop app.Who knew?So if you download the desktop app and navigate over to code,
有一點很重要需要注意，不要像我這樣把東西壓縮到一個螢幕上，要用兩個螢幕，否則 Claude 可能會搞混，以為你想要更緊湊的外觀、想調整間距什麼的。就正常操作就好，不要像我這樣壓縮畫面。我們剛才都是在終端機裡完成的，但 Claude 也有桌面應用程式。誰知道呢？所以如果你下載桌面應用程式然後切到 Code 那邊，
You can do the exact same thing as we did in Terminal, but in their desktop app.It makes things easier.I started with Terminal to get your feet up with Terminal, something us designers should know, all right?Didn't want to go the easy way out, but you can also do it inside of their desktop app.So let's do that real quick right now.So build me a black and purple dashboard, or
你可以做到跟我們在終端機裡完全一樣的事情，但是在他們的桌面應用程式裡。這讓事情變得更簡單。我從終端機開始是為了讓你先熟悉終端機，這是我們設計師應該知道的東西，好嗎？不想走捷徑，但你也可以在他們的桌面應用程式裡做。那我們現在就快速來做一下。輸入「幫我建構一個黑紫配色的儀表板」，或者
Let's go about us page, us page for a modern SaaS.And let me go ahead and actually just grab the same Figma URL.Sorry, I know you can't see the page right here, but I forgot to copy it to my clipboard.
來做一個「關於我們」頁面，給一家現代 SaaS 公司的「關於我們」頁面。讓我去拿同一個 Figma 網址。抱歉，我知道你看不到這個頁面，但我忘記複製到剪貼簿了。
So for a modern SaaS, put it in this Figma file.All right, I know, prompting's not great, but whatever.So let's go ahead, let's run that now.Now, it's important to notice you should be doing this in the same folder,But anyways, let's just run that.So now my friends, it did the exact same thing.So whether you do it in terminal, you do it in like the Claude desktop app, you know, whatever, you get a great result.It's cool.
給一家現代 SaaS 公司用，放到這個 Figma 檔案裡。好啦，我知道提示詞寫得不太好，但無所謂。那我們來執行吧。重要的是你應該在同一個資料夾裡做這件事，但不管怎樣，我們先跑吧。所以各位朋友，它做了完全一樣的事情。不管你是在終端機裡做、在 Claude 桌面應用程式裡做，還是在哪裡做，你都能得到很棒的結果。很酷。
I wanted to go through the terminal with you because it's something that we should know and we should get familiar with as more AI tools come out.It's a great thing to add to like your wheelhouse of skills and things that you're familiar with.But again, the Claude desktop app.also works too.Now, I know that's a little bit more of like a technical workflow.It's a technical tool.But there is this tool that came out called Pencil, pencil.dev, put a link for the description, where it's more of like a desire-friendly approach of working with Claude code.
我想帶你走一遍終端機的流程，是因為這是我們應該知道的東西，隨著更多 AI 工具的出現，我們應該要熟悉它。這是一個很棒的技能，可以加到你的技能庫和你熟悉的工具當中。但同樣地，Claude 桌面應用程式也可以用。接下來，我知道剛才的工作流程比較偏技術。但有一個新推出的工具叫做 Pencil，pencil.dev，我會在描述中放上連結，它更像是一種對設計師友善的方式來使用 Claude Code。
So go ahead, download Pencil, again, whether it's like the Mac version, the Windows version, or whatever, and then let's go aheadand look at this.So here I am inside of Pencil, and again, you're going to have to connect like your Claude subscription account, but you can already see how it's a much friendlier version of, you know, what we just did.So I'm going to design with Claude and just say, build me a purple dashboard for a SaaS, you know,
去下載 Pencil 吧，不管是 Mac 版、Windows 版還是什麼版本，然後我們來看看這個。這裡我已經在 Pencil 裡面了，同樣地你需要連接你的 Claude 訂閱帳號，但你已經可以看到它是一個比我們剛才做的事情友善得多的版本。我要用 Claude 來設計，就說「幫我建構一個紫色的儀表板，給一個 SaaS」，你知道的，
platform, whatever, similar prompt to what we used before.I'm just going to paste that in and then see what it comes back with.Now, one thing that's nice about this, you can see it build things in real time.I know it's going a little bit slow right now, so I'll pause.So as you can see, it's building out the dashboard in real time, which is super cool.You can see like, oh, look at that.It's adding like those dashboard cars.Super unreal.As you can see, it's thinking about everything that it's building on the left-hand side, building it out piece by piece.
平台用，隨便，跟我們之前用的差不多的提示詞。我就貼上然後看看它會回傳什麼。有一件很棒的事是，你可以看到它即時建構東西。我知道現在跑得有點慢，所以我先暫停。你可以看到它正在即時建構儀表板，超酷的。你看，噢，看那個。它正在加入那些儀表板卡片。超不真實。你可以看到它在左邊思考它正在建構的每一個東西，一塊一塊地建構出來。
I'll pause the video here and then come back once it's fully built.So look what it came back with.It came back with this dashboard.Looks pretty good.Now, it's not perfect.Like, look, this element isn't fully responsive.Not everything in here works as...as intended.But again, neither does Figma.Now, one thing that is important to note is there's currently no way to take the designs that are done here and then putting them into Figma.There's no option to do that just yet.I imagine it's in Pencil's roadmap of things that they're going to be doing.But this year looks pretty good.
我在這裡暫停影片，等它完全建構好再回來。看看它做出了什麼。它做出了這個儀表板。看起來挺不錯的。不過它不完美。看，這個元素沒有完全做到響應式。裡面不是所有東西都如預期般運作。但同樣地，Figma 也不完美啊。有一點需要注意的是，目前還沒有辦法把這裡做好的設計放進 Figma。還沒有這個選項。我想這應該在 Pencil 的產品路線圖裡。但這個結果看起來相當不錯。
It's honestly pretty a little bit better than what you generally see a lot of likeAI design tools do.But again, can't put it to Figma.So it's great if you're just sort of like looking for inspiration and want to build things out fast in a way sort of like an interface that works a little bit better for us designers.Now, one other cool feature of Pencil is they kind of have these pre-built design system or UI kits that you can choose from.
老實說它比你通常看到很多 AI 設計工具做出來的東西好一點。但同樣地，沒辦法放進 Figma。所以如果你只是在尋找靈感，想要快速建構東西，用一個對我們設計師來說更好用的介面來操作的話，它很不錯。另外 Pencil 還有一個很酷的功能，它們有一些預先建構好的設計系統或 UI 套件可以選擇。
So if you have a certain look and feel that you're going for, you can come up here, choose a kit, and have that already applied.Just a cool feature that's nice to have within Pencil.I know there's a ton goingon in this one, jump back and forth between a lot.Thanks for staying with me.If you're a big fan of myself, check out UI Collective Academy or join our free community.I'll put a link for that in the description below.And also, too, if you want to build an entire design system, click in the top left.
如果你有特定想要的風格和感覺，你可以點到上面，選一個套件，讓它直接套用。這是 Pencil 裡一個很不錯的功能。我知道這支影片內容很多，跳來跳去的。感謝你一直跟著。如果你很喜歡我，去看看 UI Collective Academy 或加入我們的免費社群。我會在下方描述中放上連結。另外，如果你想建構一整套設計系統，點左上角。
If you want to watch another video, I highly recommend it, click at the top right.Be sure to drop a subscribe, drop a like.Thanks for being here.See you at the next one.
如果你想看另一支影片，我非常推薦，點右上角。記得訂閱、按讚。感謝你的觀看。下支影片見。